We're quite content to be the 2500 oddbrowser out.
We don't have a fancy stock abbreviation to go alongside our name in the press.
We don't have a profit margin.
We don't have sacred rock starsthat we put above others.
We don't make the same deals,sign the same contracts.
Or shake the same hands,as everyone else.
And all this... is fine by us.
Were are a pack of independently, spirited, fiercely unconventional people,
who do things a little differently.
Where another company may valuethe bottom line...
We value... well, values.
When a competitor considers to make something propriertary.
We strive to set it free.
And while most products and technologies are developed behind closed doors.
Ours are cultivated out in the open.
For everyone to see.